import 'dart:ui';

import 'package:profile_app/features/profile/data/models/question_model.dart';

Color kPrimaryColor = const Color(0xff3C7098);

List<QuestionModel> questionsList = [
  QuestionModel(question: "1", correctAnswer: 'B', userAnswer: true),
  QuestionModel(question: "2", correctAnswer: 'A', userAnswer: false),
  QuestionModel(question: "3", correctAnswer: 'C', userAnswer: true),
  QuestionModel(question: "4", correctAnswer: 'A', userAnswer: true),
  QuestionModel(question: "5", correctAnswer: 'D', userAnswer: true),
  QuestionModel(question: "7", correctAnswer: 'A', userAnswer: false),
  QuestionModel(question: "8", correctAnswer: 'A', userAnswer: false),
  QuestionModel(question: "9", correctAnswer: 'B', userAnswer: true),
  QuestionModel(question: "10", correctAnswer: 'B', userAnswer: true),
  QuestionModel(question: "11", correctAnswer: 'C', userAnswer: false),
  QuestionModel(question: "12", correctAnswer: 'D', userAnswer: true),
];
